<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CinemaFuse</string>

    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="sample">test test test test test test suss mtd 319 ECA test</string>
    <string name="terminator">Release: 24-10-2019\nRunning Time: 128 minutes\nGenre: Action/Adventure\nLanguage: English (Sub: Chinese)\n\nCast: Linda Hamilton, Arnold Schwarzenegger, Mackenzie Davis, Natalia Reyes, Gabriel Luna, Diego Boneta\n\nSynopsis:\n\nMore than two decades have passed since Sarah Connor prevented Judgment Day, changed the future, and re-wrote the fate of the human race. Dani Ramos (Natalia Reyes) is living a simple life in Mexico City with her brother (Diego Boneta) and father when a highly advanced and deadly new Terminator - a Rev-9 (Gabriel Luna) - travels back through time to hunt and kill her. Dani\'s survival depends on her joining forces with two warriors: Grace (Mackenzie Davis), an enhanced super-soldier from the future, and a battle-hardened Sarah Connor (Linda Hamilton). As the Rev-9 ruthlessly destroys everything and everyone in its path on the hunt for Dani, the three are led to a T-800 (Arnold Schwarzenegger) from Sarah\'s past that may be their last best hope.</string>
    <string name="joker">Release: 03-10-2019\nRunning Time: 122 minutes\nGenre: Action/Adventure\nLanguage: English (Sub: Chinese)\n\nCast: Joaquin Phoenix, Robert De Niro, Zazie Beetz, Bill Camp, Frances Conroy, Brett Cullen, Glenn Fleshler, Douglas Hodge\n\nSynopsis:\n\nJoker centers around an origin of the iconic arch nemesis and is an original, standalone story not seen before on the big screen. Todd Phillips\' exploration of Arthur Fleck (Joaquin Phoenix), a man disregarded by society, is not only a gritty character study, but also a broader cautionary tale.</string>
    <string name="maleficent">Release: 17-10-2019\nRunning Time: 119 minutes\nGenre: Adventure/Fantasy\nLanguage: English (Sub: Chinese)\n\nCast: Angelina Jolie, Elle Fanning, Michelle Pfeiffer, Chiwetel Ejiofor, Sam Riley, Harris Dickinson, Ed Skrein, Imelda Staunton, Juno Temple, Lesley Manville\n\nSynopsis:\n\nMaleficent: Mistress of Evil" is a fantasy adventure that picks up several years after Maleficent, in which audiences learned of the events that hardened the heart of Disney's most notorious villain and drove her to curse a baby Princess Aurora. The film continues to explore the complex relationship between the horned fairy and the soon to be Queen as they form new alliances and face new adversaries in their struggle to protect the moors and the magical creatures that reside within.</string>
    <string name="dora">Release: 29-08-2019\nRunning Time: 103 minutes\nGenre: Family/Adventure\nLanguage: English (Sub: Chinese)\n\nCast: Isabela Moner, Eugenio Derbez, Michael Peña, Eva Longoria, Adriana Barraza, Temuera Morrison, Jeff Wahlberg, Nicholas Coombe, Madeleine Madden, Danny Trejo\n\nSynopsis:\n\nHaving spent most of her life exploring the jungle with her parents, nothing could prepare Dora (Isabela Moner) for her most dangerous adventure ever- High School. Always the explorer, Dora quickly finds herself leading Boots (her best friend, a monkey), Diego (Jeffrey Wahlberg), a mysterious jungle inhabitant (Eugenio Derbez), and a rag tag group of teens on a live-action adventure to save her parents (Eva Longoria, Michael Pea) and solve the impossible mystery behind a lost city of gold.</string>
    <string name="geminiman">Release: 10-10-2019\nRunning Time: 117 minutes\nGenre: Action/Adventure\nLanguage: English (Sub: Chinese)\n\nCast: Will Smith, Mary Elizabeth Winstead, Clive Owen, Benedict Wong\n\nSynopsis:\n\nGemini Man is an innovative action-thriller starring Will Smith as Henry Brogan, an elite assassin, who is suddenly targeted and pursued by a mysterious young operative that seemingly can predict his every move. The film is directed by Academy Award-winning filmmaker Ang Lee and produced by renown producers Jerry Bruckheimer, David Ellison, Dana Goldberg and Don Granger. Also starring are Mary Elizabeth Winstead, Clive Owen and Benedict Wong.</string>
</resources>
